# KYLE WAGNER

## MARKETER | DESIGNER | DEVELOPER

## SUMMARY

Marketing manager and digital designer with over four years of professional experience in Southeast Asia. Creative team player with the ability to work cross-culturally with international clients under tight deadlines. Actively learning front-end web development and UI design.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

12/2017 - Current Marketing Manager

Focus Asia Group

Implemented a complete rebranding of our luxury subbrand, Refine Asia, including sales collaterals and a handcoded website. Planned and executed a successful email marketing campaign and a social media strategy.

09/2018 - Current Web Developer, Designer

TYPE-C

Created and designed two microsite pages using Materialize CSS for a marketing campaign aimed at the Singaporean market. Designed and coded three websites using CMS for audio and video production companies.

07/2016 - 04/2019 **Project Coordinator** 

GIZ (German Society for International Cooperation)

Developed layout and panel prints for ITB Asia in Singapore for 2 years. Assisted in the development of a booth in Paksé, Laos. Designed a parade banner for *Khiaw*, a sustainability project in Luang Prabang. Created presentations and posters for investors to follow UNESCO regulations.

09/2014 - 09/2017 **Marketing Coordinator** 

Tiger Trail Travel

Redesigned entire visual communication platform including print-based advertisements, tour catalogues, logos, and business cards. Developed two responsive websites on Wordpress: Fairtrek.org & Biking-Laos.com.

## **SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

Photoshop	Adobe XD	
Illustrator	Zeplin	
InDesign	HTML/CSS	
Sketch	Javascript	

#### **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2017

MA Geography
York University, Toronto, CANADA

2012 - 2014

BA International Studies (Honors)
DePaul University, Chicago, USA

# SOCIAL

in Linkedin.com/in/kyledwagner

O Instagram.com/kyledwagner

(C) +66 80 362 0972